In this video, I'm going to show you how
to use the C6 2.5 long video mode.
>> Hi.
>> Hey. Hi.
Sorry. Our car died a couple miles down.
>> It's just
I'm out here on my own.
>> Right. No, yeah. Totally get it.
>> You guys aren't like serial killers, are
you?
>> Left the ax in the car.
>> God. Okay.
Come in.
>> This is Thank you, really. You saved us
out there.
>> Glad it was my porch. There's nobody
else's for miles.
>> You live up here alone?
>> With my grandma. It's her house.
>> Is she home?
>> No. Hospital.
Is she okay?
She has good days.
So,
are you two a thing?
>> Us? No. No way.
>> Just friends.
Good to know. It gets incredibly quiet
out here. Sometimes you just need
company.
>> Well, we're glad we found this place. We
would have frozen out there.
This is Thank you, really. You saved us
out there.
>> Glad it was my porch. There's nobody
else's for miles.
>> You live up here alone?
>> With my grandpa. It's her house.
>> Is she home?
>> No. Hospital.
Is she okay?
She has good days.
So,
are you two a thing?
>> Us? No. No way.
>> Just friends.
>> I lost my license, so she's been helping
me out. Long story, boring one. She
drives, I ride shotgun and pay for gas.
>> He doesn't pay for gas.
>> I emotionally pay for gas.
>> Where's your bathroom? Down the hall on
the right. Door sticks, you have to lift
the handle up while you push. Don't ask
me why.
>> So, as you can see, we're here in
Dreamina's website. Now, as far as I
know, this is exclusive to Dreamina
only. If you try this with CapCut,
CapCut's actually going to give you
multiple clips instead of just one video
clip, like it would here in Dreamina.
Now, to use it, it's very simple. Just
go to AI video,
change it to Dreamina Sea Dance 2.5, and
down here, you will see long video. What
that's going to do now is open up this
new option. What this is going to allow
you to do now is select a duration that
goes past 30 seconds. Now, as you can
see, 39,420
credits is how much it's going to cost
for me to generate a 1 3-minute video.
I'll put the actual conversion in the
pinned comments below, so you can check
out how much that is in US dollars. Now,
currently, I was not able to do the
whole full 3 minutes. I tried 30
seconds, 45 seconds, and then a 1 full
minute. I am going to keep trying, but I
keep getting an error whenever I try to
do the 3 minutes. I tried it for like 5
hours yesterday. Now, that said, one of
the things you're going to run into when
you're trying to do a full 1 minute 3
minute is that you will hit that 5,000
character limit in Dreamina. For the 1
minute, actually, I had to use the
oldest trick which is converting
everything to Chinese to shrink the
prompt, but if we're talking 3 minutes
with dialogue, that 5,000 characters is
just not going to do it.
All right, so let's talk about this real
quick. From my experience right now
testing this out, you're not going to
get a fully
continuous
45 seconds, 1 minute, 3 minute clip.
There's going to be cuts in there, and
I'm sure you probably heard it, but if
you didn't, check this out.
>> Is she okay?
>> See that? You hear that stop there?
Actually, if you open up the
if you open it up,
>> Is she okay?
>> Right here.
This is where that stopped. You can hear
it click. So, it's not really like one
continuous it does click. Additionally,
similar to the extend function in 2.0,
it does degrade image just a little bit.
Now, it's it's not as bad as 2.0's
extend function, I don't think, up to 1
minute, but it does degrade it just just
a little bit, ever so slightly. All
right, so this is the 1-minute one, and
again, you're going to be able to tell
where the cut is around 30 seconds.
And the trick part is this had a lot of
dialogue in it, right? I filled it up up
to 1 minute from my script, so it was
basically doing the pace for me of the
cut conversation, but what I noticed is
that
it was kind of speeding up,
and then get to the 30 second,
and then there's a little bit of pauses
towards the end, there's a big pause.
So, it was directing the pacing for me.
So, what I'm trying to say is if you
want to direct your pace of the
dialogue,
if you're very picky with how you want
it paced, you're going to have to be
very careful with this
because when using the long video mode,
it basically decides for you.
Yes, you can timestamp it if you want,
but I do not suggest doing that because
the pacing gets even worse. So, will I
be using this tool?
I think in certain scenarios,
absolutely. I think it's super helpful.
It's much easier than my workaround on
getting a 30 45 to a minute clip, I can
tell you that right now, because there's
really no manual work to it. See that
2.5 and Germaine is doing all the work.
So, yes, it is still in beta.
One day, hopefully, we can actually get
this to work for the entire 1 minute and
there's no dropping quality and it's one
continuous motion. All right, so with
that said, that's pretty much it for
this video. I hope you all learned
something new today. If you haven't done
so, go ahead and like and comment to
help me with the SEO algorithm. Uh with
that said, I'll see you all in the next
one. Peace out.
>> [music]